table 1 page 11 row 0 col 0 to 1	Name	t156l180w30h13
table 1 page 11 row 0 col 1 to 2	Position(s) Held	t156l509w82h13
table 1 page 11 row 0 col 2 to 3	Age	t156l804w20h13
table 1 page 11 row 1 col 0 to 1	Richard J. Kramer	t173l134w123h17
table 1 page 11 row 1 col 1 to 2	Chairman of the Board, Chief Executive Officer and President 	t173l396w198h17
table 1 page 11 row 1 col 2 to 3	49	t173l793w15h17
table 1 page 11 row 2 col 0 to 1	Mr. Kramer was elected Chief Executive Officer and President effective April 13, 2010 and Chairman effective October 1, 2010. He is the principal executive officer of the Company. Mr. Kramer joined Goodyear in March 2000 and has served as Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer (June 2004 to August 2007), President, North American Tire (March 2007 to February 2010) and Chief Operating Officer (June 2009 to April 2010). t208l80w370h17
table 1 page 11 row 2 col 1 to 2		t0l0w0h0
table 1 page 11 row 2 col 2 to 3		t0l0w0h0
table 1 page 11 row 3 col 0 to 1	Darren R. Wells	t290l143w105h17
table 1 page 11 row 3 col 1 to 2	Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer	t290l381w339h17
table 1 page 11 row 3 col 2 to 3	47	t290l789w15h17
table 1 page 11 row 4 col 0 to 1	Mr. Wells was named Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer in October 2008. He is Goodyear's principal financial officer. Mr. Wells joined Goodyear in August 2002 and has served as Senior Vice President, Business Development and Treasurer (May 2005 to March 2007) and Senior Vice President, Finance and Strategy (March 2007 to October 2008). 	t312l80w648h17
table 1 page 11 row 4 col 1 to 2		t0l0w0h0
table 1 page 11 row 4 col 2 to 3		t0l0w0h0
table 1 page 11 row 5 col 0 to 1	Stephen R. McClellan	t389l125w140h17
table 1 page 11 row 5 col 1 to 2	President, North American Tire	t389l448w205h17
table 1 page 11 row 5 col 2 to 3	47	t389l793w15h17
table 1 page 11 row 6 col 0 to 1	Mr. McClellan was named President, North American Tire on August 18, 2011. He is the executive officer responsible for Goodyear's operations in North America. Mr. McClellan joined Goodyear in 1988 and has served as Vice President, Goodyear Commercial Tire Systems (September 2003 to August 2008) and President, Consumer Tires, North American Tire (August 2008 to August 2011). 	t412l80w100h17
table 1 page 11 row 6 col 1 to 2		t0l0w0h0
table 1 page 11 row 6 col 2 to 3		t0l0w0h0
table 1 page 11 row 7 col 0 to 1	Arthur de Bok	t482l148w94h17
table 1 page 11 row 7 col 1 to 2	President, Europe, Middle East and Africa Tire	t482l398w305h17
table 1 page 11 row 7 col 2 to 3	50	t482l793w15h17
table 1 page 11 row 8 col 0 to 1	Mr. de Bok was named President, Europe, Middle East and Africa Tire effective February 1, 2008. He is the executive officer responsible for Goodyear's operations in Europe, the Middle East and Africa. Mr. de Bok joined Goodyear in January 2002 and has served as President, European Union Tire (September 2005 to January 2008). 	t505l80w488h17
table 1 page 11 row 8 col 1 to 2		t0l0w0h0
table 1 page 11 row 8 col 2 to 3		t0l0w0h0
table 1 page 11 row 9 col 0 to 1	Jaime Cohen Szulc	t569l134w122h17
table 1 page 11 row 9 col 1 to 2	President, Latin American Tire	t569l450w202h17
table 1 page 11 row 9 col 2 to 3	50	t569l793w15h17